<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Module_2_Lesson_5_hw_2</string>

    <string name="title_main_news">Audi and Moto List :)</string>
    <string name="like_number">0</string>
    <string name="button_home">HOME</string>

    <string name="comments_title_1">Ivan Kozak</string>
    <string name="comments_description_1">I love this car :)</string>
    <string name="comments_title_2">Bohdan Khmelnytskyi</string>
    <string name="comments_description_2">I wish we have this type of cars in our century.</string>
    <string name="comments_title_3">Michael Shumakher</string>
    <string name="comments_description_3">I\'ve driven faster car than this one.</string>

    <string name="news_title_1">Audi A3 First Generation</string>
    <string name="news_description_1">The original A3 (or Type 8L) was announced back in June 1995,
        but introduced first in the European market for more than year in September 1996, marking
        Audi\'s return to the production of smaller cars following the demise of the Audi 50 in
        1978. This was the first Volkswagen Group model to use the "PQ34" or "A4" platform,
        bearing a close resemblance to the contemporary Volkswagen Golf Mk4, which arrived a year
        later. Within three years, this platform was used for total of seven cars.The A3 was
        initially available only with a three-door hatchback body, to present a more sporty image
        than the Golf, in both front and four-wheel drive. The inline four-cylinder engines were
        transversely mounted. The Audi A3 was the eighth model in the Audi lineup to use five
        valves per cylinder.</string>
    <string name="news_title_2">Audi A3 Second Generation</string>
    <string name="news_description_2">At the 2003 Geneva Motor Show, Audi launched the second
        generation of the A3, the Typ 8P, designed by Gary Telaak during 2000 (however, the final
        design was frozen in 2001). Originally launched only as a three-door hatchback with
        four-cylinder engines, it featured a new automobile platform (the PQ35 platform), a
        redesigned and more spacious interior, new petrol engines with Fuel Stratified Injection
        (FSI), and standard six-speed manual gearboxes (except on the base 1.6). In mid-2003 the
        line was updated with two sports-oriented models, a 2.0 Turbo-FSI version rated 200 PS
        (147 kW; 197 hp), and a 3.2 L VR6 engine (for the first time) with 250 PS (184 kW; 247 hp).
        Haldex Traction-based quattro on-demand four-wheel drive, and the S-Tronic semi-auto
        gearbox were introduced as options (quattro is standard on the VR6) on models with engines
        over 140 PS (103 kW; 138 hp). In 2005 the "S line" trim level, offering new decorative
        elements, became available and the three-door A3 received the same front-end styling
        features as the Sportback model. For the first time, the A3 became available in the
        North American market, exclusively with the Sportback body, with the base 2.0 inline-four
        FSI introduced in 2005 as a 2006 model, and the 3.2 VR6 Quattro following.</string>
    <string name="news_title_3">Audi A3 Third Generation</string>
    <string name="news_description_3">The vehicle was unveiled at the 2012 Geneva Motor Show and
        went on sale in Europe in September 2012. First vehicle using the flexible modular
        Volkswagen Group MQB platform, the third generation is available as a three-door hatchback,
        a five-door "Sportback", a four-door saloon to directly rival the Mercedes-Benz CLA-Class,
        and a two-door Cabriolet. The front suspension is a MacPherson strut set-up while the rear
        utilizes torsion bar suspension (models with less than 150 PS) or multi-link rear
        suspension (models with 150 PS or more).</string>

    <string name="news_title_4">Audi A3 Fourth Generation</string>
    <string name="news_description_4">The new A3 was unveiled online in 2020. The new interior
        and exterior styling is heavily inspired by Lamborghini, LED headlights and taillights,
        with the option of Matrix and Laser LED headlights. It shares the MQB evo platform with
        other Audi models, and with the Volkswagen Golf Mk8, SEAT Leon Mk4, and Škoda Octavia Mk4.
        It is 3 centimetres longer and wider when compared to the outgoing model while keeping the
        wheelbase length the same, trunk cargo space is 380 litres with the seats up, and 1200
        litres with the seats folded down. It has a drag coefficient of 0.28, and is powered by
        1.0-liter 3-cylinder gasoline turbocharged engine with 110 hp, 1.5-litre with 150 hp,
        2.0-liter TDI with 116 hp or 150 hp. There is also a new 2.0-liter Quattro version in both
        gasoline and diesel variants. It produces 190 hp (142 kW) and 320 N⋅m (236 lbf⋅ft) of
        torque (400 Nm for the diesel variant). It also has reduced cargo space (320 litres
        instead of the 380 litres in the other A3 variants) due to the Quattro four-wheel-drive
        system.</string>

    <string name="news_title_5">Audi S3 First Generation</string>
    <string name="news_description_5">Audi released the A3-derived Audi S3 in 1999, only as a
        three-door hatchback. The inline-four 20v 1.8 L turbocharged petrol engine came in two
        versions: 210 PS (154 kW; 207 hp) and 225 PS (165 kW; 222 hp). Early models (1999–2001)
        had 210 PS (154 kW; 207 hp). Later models (2001–2003) had variable valve timing and 225 PS
        (165 kW; 222 hp). The engine had a maximum of 280 N⋅m (210 ft⋅lbf) torque. This was the
        first time a small four-cylinder engine had been used in an Audi S-series car.</string>

    <string name="news_title_6">Audi S3 Second Generation</string>
    <string name="news_description_6">In August 2006, Audi introduced the second generation S3.
        Offered in three- and five-door body styles, the second generation—Typ 8P—S3 is powered
        by a modified and uprated Volkswagen Group-sourced 2.0-litre turbocharged FSI petrol
        engine, with a maximum output of 195 kW (265 PS; 261 bhp). As with all Audi S models,
        the design was done in-house by quattro GmbH. The engine features uprated high-performance
        pistons, revised boost/fuel mapping, increased turbocharger size (KKK K04) and larger
        intercooler. The most powerful form of this engine, and quattro four-wheel drive, makes
        for a 0–100 km/h (0–62 mph) time of 5.5 seconds, and an electronically limited top speed
        of 250 km/h (155 mph). Audi offers both six-speed manual and six-speed S-Tronic automatic
        transmissions with the S3. The spring ratings and dampers were revised, along with the
        body kit. Like its predecessor, although badged a "Quattro" model, the S3 does not employ
        a Torsen centre differential (as in other common Quattro models), but instead uses the
        Swedish Haldex Traction system in its on-demand four-wheel drive transmission, due to the
        transverse engine layout.</string>

    <string name="news_title_7">Audi S3 Third Generation</string>
    <string name="news_description_7">The third generation Audi S3 is powered by a 2.0 L; 121.1
        cu in (1,984 cc) TFSI (turbo gasoline direct injection) inline-four engine, with an output
        of 221 kW (300 PS; 296 bhp) at 5,500 rpm and 380 N⋅m (280 lbf⋅ft) of torque at 1,800-5,500
        rpm, with its redline at 6,800 rpm. It features new pistons with stronger bolts and
        new rings, as well as reinforced connecting rods with new mounts transferring the power
        to the crankshaft. The cylinder head is made of a new lightweight aluminium alloy designed
        with high strength and temperature resistance in mind. It has a combined fuel economy of
        23 mpg‑US (10 L/100 km; 28 mpg‑imp) manual; and 24 mpg‑US (9.8 L/100 km; 29 mpg‑imp) with
        S tronic. The engine weighs in at 148 kg (326 lb), 5 kg (11 lb) lighter than the previous
        generation. The S3 is capable of 0–100 km/h (62 mph) in 4.8-5.2 seconds and has an
        electronically limited top speed of 155 mph (249 km/h).</string>

    <string name="news_title_8">Audi S3 Fourth Generation</string>
    <string name="news_description_8">The S3 model has the same 2.0L petrol engine from the
        previous generation, producing 310 hp (231 kW) and 400 N⋅m (295 lbf⋅ft) of torque, but
        this time is only available with an automatic gearbox. Similarly it has reduced cargo
        space due to the Quattro four-wheel-drive system. Like the previous generation, the new
        S3 also comes as a saloon/sedan.</string>

    <string name="news_title_9">Audi RS 3 Sportback (2011–2012)</string>
    <string name="news_description_9">The Audi RS 3 is derivative of the A3 Sportback with a
        5-cylinder, 2,480 cc (151 cu in) turbocharged engine rated at 340 PS (250 kW; 335 hp)
        and 450 N⋅m (332 lb⋅ft), vermicular-graphite cast iron crankcase, seven-speed S tronic
        transmission with two automatic modes and one manual mode, Quattro on-demand four-wheel
        drive system, widened track to 1,564 mm (61.57 in), MacPherson strut in aluminum, lowered
        body by 25 mm (0.98 in), 19-inch cast aluminum wheels in machine-polished titanium
        styling (optional black with a red rim flange) with 235/35 front and 225/35 rear tires,
        370 mm (14.57 in) front and 310 mm (12.20 in) ventilated brake discs, aluminum brake disk
        covers, four-piston fixed calipers in high-gloss black with RS logos, electronic
        stabilization program with Sport mode, flared front fenders made of carbon-fiber-reinforced
        plastic (CFRP), prominent sill panels and exterior-mirror casings in matte aluminum, roof
        spoiler, high-gloss black diffuser insert, two elliptical exhaust tailpipes on the left,
        black interior, sports seats upholstered in Nappa leather with silver contrasting stitching,
        inlays in Piano black finish or Aluminum Race colour, flat-bottomed leather multifunction
        sports steering wheel, choice of 5 body colors are available with an unlimited selection
        of custom paint finishes. Its acceleration is quoted as 0 to 62 mph (0 to 100 km/h) in 4.6
        seconds, with an electronically limited top speed of 155 mph (249 km/h). Optional features
        included front bucket seats, roof rails in matte aluminum look, styling packages in black
        or matte aluminum.</string>

    <string name="news_title_10">Audi RS 3 (2015–2020)</string>
    <string name="news_description_10">Details for the RS 3 Sportback were revealed in December
        2014. It went on sale in the first quarter of 2015 and featured a 2.5 litres (2,480 cc)
        straight-5 engine with 367 PS (270 kW; 362 hp) and 465 N⋅m (343 lbf⋅ft) of torque. The RS 3
        Sportback is equipped with 7-speed dual clutch S tronic transmission and quattro all-wheel
        drive system. Scott Keogh of Audi of America said in April 2015 that he\'s "confident"
        we\'ll see the car come to the United States. In 2017, the RS3 sedan or saloon was added
        to the line-up. The RS3 can be ordered with a fixed-suspension or an adjustable magnetic
        damper. Depending on the country, the RS3 can be purchased with different optional
        packages. For example, the Black Optic package includes high-gloss black 19-inch wheels,
        high-gloss black outside mirror covers, and a high-gloss black trunk lip spoiler, while
        the Dynamic package consists of titanium 19-inch wheels with summer performance tires,
        red brake calipers, and a sport exhaust system.</string>

    <string name="news_title_11">Audi RS 3 (2020-present)</string>
    <string name="news_description_11">The highest specification RS 3 model is fitted with a
        2.5-litre 5-cylinder producing 400 hp (298 kW) and 500 N⋅m (369 lbf⋅ft), and has 0-60 mph
        (97 km/h) acceleration time of just 3.8 seconds. It gets a seven-speed dual-clutch
        automatic, or an electric S-Tronic gearbox. It also gets the new MMI infotainment system,
        with a 10.25 or 12.3-inch digital instrument cluster, and a secondary screen of
        10.1-inches.</string>

    <string name="news_title_12">Husqvarna Motorcycles</string>
    <string name="news_description_12">Husqvarna Motorcycles GmbH (marketed as Husqvarna) is a
        Swedish-origin Austrian company which designs, engineers, manufactures and distributes
        motocross, enduro, supermoto and street motorcycles. The company began producing
        motorcycles in 1903 at Huskvarna, Sweden, as a subsidiary of the Husqvarna armament
        firm. Today, Husqvarna Motorcycles GmbH is owned by PIERER Mobility Group.</string>

    <string name="news_title_13">KTM</string>
    <string name="news_description_13">KTM AG (Kraftfahrzeug Trunkenpolz Mattighofen, formerly KTM
        Sportmotorcycle AG) is an Austrian motorcycle, bicycle and sports car manufacturer owned
        by Pierer Mobility AG and Indian manufacturer Bajaj Auto International Holdings BV. It was
        formed in 1992 but traces its foundation to as early as 1934. Today, KTM AG is the parent
        company of the KTM Group, consisting of a number of motorcycle brands. KTM is known for
        its off-road motorcycles (enduro, motocross and supermoto). Since the late 1990s, it has
        expanded into street motorcycle production and developing sports cars – namely the X-Bow.
        In 2015, KTM sold almost as many street as off-road bikes. From 2012, KTM was the largest
        motorcycle manufacturer in Europe for four consecutive years. Globally, the company is
        among the leading off-road motorcycle manufacturers. In 2016, KTM sold 203,423 motor
        vehicles worldwide</string>

    <string name="news_title_14">Gas Gas</string>
    <string name="news_description_14">Gas Gas is a Spanish motorcycle manufacturer established
        in 1985.</string>

    <string name="news_title_15">Honda CRF Series</string>
    <string name="news_description_15">The Honda CRF series is a line of four-stroke motocross,
        trail, and dual sport motorcycles manufactured and marketed by Honda. The CRF line was
        launched in 2000 as a successor to the Honda CR series.</string>
</resources>